

BRENT VANWILDEMEERSCH SOFTWARE ENGINEER

### **DETAILS**

Brussels, Belgium

vanwildemeersch.bre nt@gmail.com

vanwildemeersch.bre nt.github.io

# LANGUAGES

Dutch NATIVE French **PROFICIENT FLUENT** English

# **SKILLS**

JS/TS (Vue.js, Angular, React, ReactNative, ES6 Redux, Vuex, Styled Components, Storybook)

HTML5, CSS, LESS/SASS

Cypress, Jest

Git, CI/CD, DevOps basics

Linux and Windows PHP and Wordpress

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

Professional Scrum Master (PSM1)

AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner

# **PROFILE**

Software engineer with 6 years of experience. A dedicated problem solver and expert skills in JavaScript and supporting languages/libraries and frameworks that solve real world problems through code.

Eager to learn and always open to explore new things

Flexible person who can adapt quickly to changing circumstances

# CAREER OBJECTIVE

Problem solver and strong communicator. Eager to prove my value and talent. Motivated to advance and expand my skill set through challenging projects. I enjoy working collaboratively, but can run projects independently. Focused on developing scalable and well-documented software solutions

# **EDUCATION**

2013 - 2017 Bachelor of New Media and Communication Technologies

Hogeschool West-Vlaanderen - Kortrijk, Belgium

Industrial Sciences 2007 - 2013

Vrij Technisch Instituut- Poperinge, Belgium

# EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

### SOFTWARE ENGINEER (FOR POSITIVE THINKING COMPANY)

November 2020 - Current | Easyfairs

# Brussels, Belgium

- Development and maintenance of inhouse products used by clients and by staff
- Development and engineering of prototypes for new features and future
- Improve reliability and customer satisfaction of software applications
- Collaborating with back-end, dev-ops and security team to improve workflows and security
- Development of custom WordPress plugins and themes to facilitate the business

#### SOFTWARE ENGINEERING CONSULTANT

September 2020 - Current | Positive Thinking Company

#### Brussels, Belaium

- Guidance of junior Javascript developers in their growth path
- Part of the internal Javascript community
- · Sharing knowledge during KSS (Knowledge Sharing Sessions) about software development, architecture to other consultants, Business Managers, ...
- Conducting technical interviews to assess the skills and abilities of potential candidates

#### **FULL-STACK DEVELOPER**

July 2017 - August 2020 | Ocular

# Zwevezele, Belgium

- Development of audio-visual interactives
  Engineering & architecture of inhouse CMS platform to provide audio-visual interactives of content
- Development of custom CMS platforms as Lead Developer
- Development of custom software solutions

# MOBILE APP DEVELOPER (INTERN)

February 2017 - June 2017 | University of the Western Cape

#### Cape Town, South Africa

- Internship at the Colab for Social Innovation and E-Inclusion
- Development of the University app to create micro-communities on campus
- Guiding starting Computer Science students on their path to become a software developer
- Briefing of stakeholders about upcoming features and releases
- Charity work by giving Java-classes to high-school students around Cape Town.